<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rumspring Fellowship</title>
    <link>https://rumspring.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rumspring Fellowship</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 12:00:29 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rumspring.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Rumspring</title>
      <link>https://rumspring.org/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 12:00:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumspring.org/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>More than four centuries ago in Zurich, Switzerland, a new fellowship of Christian believers was formed. The churches of the day had become unspeakably corrupt. Martin Luther had separated himself from it but had continued the un-Scriptural practice of infant baptism. Ulrich Zwingli also had separated from Romanism, but continued to grant to the political rulers the right to decide the policies and practices of the church.
The new fellowship, led by Conrad Grebel and Feliz Manz, was formed to give men and women the opportunity to follow the Lord Jesus Christ according to the whole Word of God, the Bible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rumspring Beliefs</title>
      <link>https://rumspring.org/posts/beliefs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 12:00:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumspring.org/posts/beliefs/</guid>
      <description>While many assume that the core beliefs of the Amish and Mennonites are the same as others in nominal Christianity, that&amp;rsquo;s not really true. Yes, we believe that we are saved by the work of Jesus on the cross and that no amount of good works will bring us into right standing with God.
But as it says in Romans 3:25 it is for &amp;ldquo;remission of sins that are past&amp;rdquo;. The book of James describes the qualities of the living faith that is accepted by God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Rumspring</title>
      <link>https://rumspring.org/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 12:00:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rumspring.org/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>We are a new Amish Christian fellowship seeking to understand and follow the teachings of Jesus.
Join us for fellowship in South Austin every Sunday morning at 10am.
We meet at 4200 Cortina Drive.
Learn more about our beliefs and our history.
We invite you to join us as we follow Jesus in community.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
